Conversation Flow (checking for missed transitions):
>> ID: 0 | Role: Operator   | Ladies and gentlemen, thank you for standing by, and welcome to the Lilly Q..
>> ID: 0 | Role: Operator   | Thank you, Paul, and good morning, everyone. Thank you for joining us for E..
   ID: 0 | Role: Executive  | Okay. Thanks, Joe. We're pleased with our Q1 results and the continued mome..
   ID: 0 | Role: Executive  | Thanks, Dave. Slide 6 summarizes financial performance in the first quarter..
>> ID: 0 | Role: Executive  | Thanks, Anat. Let me start with our exciting announcement from earlier this..
>> ID: 0 | Role: Executive  | Thanks, Anat. Let me start with our exciting announcement from earlier this..
   ID: 0 | Role: Executive  | Okay. Thanks, Dan. Before we go to Q&A, let me briefly sum up the progress ..
>> ID: 0 | Role: Executive  | Thanks, Dave. We'd like to take questions from as many callers as possible ..
>> ID: 0 | Role: Operator   | [Operator Instructions] The first question today is coming from Chris Schot..
>> ID: 0 | Role: Analyst    | Congrats on the progress here. I just had a question, just was hoping you c..
   ID: 0 | Role: Executive  | Thanks, Chris. I'll hand over to Anat to talk about the guidance raise.
>> ID: 0 | Role: Executive  | Thanks for the question, Chris. And as we've mentioned earlier in the year ..
>> ID: 1 | Role: Operator   | The next question is coming from Mohit Bansal from Wells Fargo.
>> ID: 1 | Role: Analyst    | I have a question regarding the pricing. So if you look at the script trend..
   ID: 1 | Role: Analyst    | Thanks, Mohit. You didn't say it, but I assume you're talking about Mounjar..
   ID: 1 | Role: Executive  | Thank you very much, Mohit. When you look at the pricing of Mounjaro, I thi..
>> ID: 2 | Role: Operator   | The next question is coming from Umer Raffat from Evercore.
>> ID: 2 | Role: Analyst    | I wanted to focus a quick second on Part D reimbursement dynamics, if I may..
>> ID: 2 | Role: Executive  | Thanks, Umer. I'll go to Patrik for that question.
   ID: 2 | Role: Executive  | Thank you very much, Umer. I think with the announcement made by the CMS ea..
>> ID: 3 | Role: Operator   | The next question is coming from Seamus Fernandez from Guggenheim.
   ID: 0 | Role: Analyst    | Great. So really just wanted to ask, Dan, as you have assessed the Phase II..
   ID: 0 | Role: Executive  | Dan?
   ID: 0 | Role: Executive  | Thanks, Seamus. So I'll start with the last part there. Yes, the abstract w..
>> ID: 1 | Role: Operator   | The next question will be from Tim Anderson from Wolfe Research.
   ID: 1 | Role: Analyst    | You showed a slide, Zepbound has NBRx share market of 57% end of Q1. That m..
   ID: 1 | Role: Executive  | Thanks, Tim. Okay. I'll maybe hand to Dan for some comments.
   ID: 1 | Role: Executive  | Yes, sure, Tim. It's probably more of your job than ours to speculate on co..
>> ID: 2 | Role: Operator   | The next question will be from Terence Flynn from Morgan Stanley.
   ID: 2 | Role: Analyst    | Congrats on all the progress. Just was wondering if you can tell us if the ..
>> ID: 2 | Role: Executive  | Thanks for the question, Terence. I'll hand to Patrik for commentary on IQV..
   ID: 2 | Role: Executive  | Thanks very much, Terence. When it comes to LillyDirect, I think we are ver..
>> ID: 3 | Role: Operator   | The next question will be from Akash Tewari from Jefferies.
   ID: 3 | Role: Analyst    | So your team presented data on a monotherapy GIP agonist at ADA last year, ..
   ID: 3 | Role: Executive  | Thank you, Akash. I'll hand to Dan for a commentary on our amylin.
>> ID: 3 | Role: Executive  | Yes, there are a lot of good questions in there. Thanks for following so cl..
>> ID: 4 | Role: Operator   | The next question will be from Trung Huynh from UBS.
   ID: 4 | Role: Analyst    | Just back on CMS recently broadening its coverage for Wegovy for certain he..
   ID: 4 | Role: Executive  | Thanks, Trung. I'll let Patrik respond.
   ID: 4 | Role: Executive  | Thanks, Trung. Now based upon what CMS stated early April, we actually expe..
>> ID: 5 | Role: Operator   | The next question will be from Geoff Meacham from Bank of America.
   ID: 0 | Role: Analyst    | You guys have been asked on this before, I'm sure, but can you just review ..
>> ID: 0 | Role: Executive  | Thanks, Geoff, for the question. Paul -- Dave, you want to weigh in? .
   ID: 0 | Role: Executive  | Yes. Sure. And Ilya can add to this. As we think we've said on several call..
>> ID: 1 | Role: Operator   | The next question is from Kerry Holford from Berenberg.
   ID: 1 | Role: Analyst    | I'm going to take a different topic here. Looking LP(a), your new product y..
>> ID: 1 | Role: Executive  | Thanks, Kerry. So a good multipart question, but on Lp(a), happy to talk ab..
>> ID: 1 | Role: Executive  | Yes. Thanks, Kerry, for the good questions here. You're right, we haven't y..
>> ID: 2 | Role: Operator   | The next question will be from Steve Scala from TD Cowen.
   ID: 2 | Role: Analyst    | Given that based on all available metrics, the SURPASS-CVOT interim likely ..
>> ID: 2 | Role: Executive  | Thanks, Steve. Dan, do you want to take the question on SURPASS-CVOT?
   ID: 2 | Role: Executive  | Sure. Thanks, Steve. As you know, we do our best not to comment on interim ..
>> ID: 3 | Role: Operator   | The next question will be from Evan Seigerman from BMO Capital Markets.
   ID: 3 | Role: Analyst    | I wanted to touch on donanemab with the AdCom approaching. Can you discuss ..
   ID: 3 | Role: Executive  | Thanks, Evan. Anne, you want to discuss [ donanemab ] and AdCom?
>> ID: 3 | Role: Executive  | Yes. Thanks so much for the question. And we are incredibly confident in do..
>> ID: 4 | Role: Operator   | Next question will be from David Risinger from Leerink Partners.
>> ID: 4 | Role: Analyst    | And let me add my congrats on the progress and the guidance raise. So my qu..
>> ID: 4 | Role: Operator   | Thanks, Dave. I'll hand over to our Dave Ricks here.
   ID: 4 | Role: Executive  | Okay. Great. Dave, great to hear from you. I mean, first of all, it is true..
>> ID: 5 | Role: Operator   | Next question is coming from Louise Chen from Cantor.
